{
    "video_id": "7L24jMxYr8M",
    "title": "Sam Bankman-Fried sentenced to 25 years for FTX fraud",
    "channel": "The Verge",
    "channel_id": "UCddiUEpeqJcYeBxX1IVBKvQ",
    "subscriber_count": 3390000,
    "upload_date": "2024-03-28T18:58:04Z",
    "video_url": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7L24jMxYr8M",
    "category": "Science & Technology",
    "tags": [
        "gadgets",
        "tech gadgets",
        "technology",
        "verge",
        "the verge",
        "tech",
        "tech news",
        "ftx",
        "crypto"
    ],
    "views": 23968,
    "likes": 574,
    "comments_count": 31,
    "description": "FTX co-founder Sam Bankman-Fried was sentenced to a total of 300 months, or 25 years, in prison for seven counts of conspiracy and fraud charges stemming from the collapse of the crypto exchange he started.\n\nSubscribe: http://goo.gl/G5RXGs\nLike The Verge on Facebook: https://goo.gl/2P1aGc\nFollow on Twitter: https://goo.gl/XTWX61\nFollow on Instagram: https://goo.gl/7ZeLvX\nFollow on TikTok: http://bit.ly/42VeCVU\n\nThe Vergecast Podcast: https://pod.link/430333725\nDecoder with Nilay Patel: http://apple.co/3v29nDc \nMore about our podcasts: https://www.theverge.com/podcasts\n\nRead More: http://www.theverge.com\nCommunity guidelines: http://bit.ly/2D0hlAv\nWallpapers from The Verge: https://bit.ly/2xQXYJr\n\nSubscribe to The Vergecast on YouTube, new episodes on Tuesday and Friday: https://bit.ly/3I6nJtz\n\nIf you buy something from a Verge link, Vox Media may receive a commission without exerting any influence on editorial content. For more information about our ethics policy, visit: https://www.theverge.com/ethics-state...",
    "description_links": [
        "http://goo.gl/G5RXGs",
        "https://goo.gl/2P1aGc",
        "https://goo.gl/XTWX61",
        "https://goo.gl/7ZeLvX",
        "http://bit.ly/42VeCVU",
        "https://pod.link/430333725",
        "http://apple.co/3v29nDc",
        "https://www.theverge.com/podcasts",
        "http://www.theverge.com",
        "http://bit.ly/2D0hlAv",
        "https://bit.ly/2xQXYJr",
        "https://bit.ly/3I6nJtz",
        "https://www.theverge.com/ethics-state..."
    ],
    "transcript": "Sam Bankman-Fried has been sentenced to 25 years in prison. He was arrested last year following the catastrophic collapse of FTX, the cryptocurrency exchange he co-founded in 2019. The sentence is about half of the 40 to 50 years that prosecuters wanted, but it's also not as short as the five to six years that Bankman-Fried's lawyers wanted. During sentencing, Judge Lewis Kaplan didn't buy into the defense's claim that Bankman-Fried was deeply sorry for what he has done. Instead, Kaplan said Bankman-Fried knew what he was doing was wrong, and that he was aware he was putting customers' money at risk. He also dismissed arguments that FTX customers could be repaid with crypto prices rebounding, and FTX's investment into an AI company. As Judge Kaplan put it, a thief who takes his loot to Las Vegas and successfully bets the stolen money is not entitled to a discount on the sentence by using his Las Vegas winnings to pay back all or part of which he stole when he finally gets caught. Bankman-Fried has been in the Metropolitan Detention Center in Brooklyn, New York since violating the conditions of his bail last year.",
    "transcript_keywords": [
        "Judge Lewis Kaplan",
        "Sam BankmanFried",
        "Las Vegas",
        "BankmanFried",
        "Judge Kaplan put",
        "FTX",
        "Kaplan",
        "Judge Kaplan",
        "Lewis Kaplan",
        "Metropolitan Detention Center",
        "years",
        "Judge Lewis",
        "BankmanFried lawyers wanted",
        "Las Vegas winnings",
        "year",
        "Judge",
        "Sam",
        "prison",
        "Center in Brooklyn",
        "Las"
    ],
    "transcript_entities": [
        [
            "Bankman-Fried",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "last year",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "New York",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "about half",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the Metropolitan Detention Center",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Bankman-Fried's",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "FTX",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Sam Bankman-Fried",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Lewis Kaplan",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Kaplan",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Las Vegas",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "25 years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "2019",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Brooklyn",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "the five to six years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "AI",
            "ORG"
        ]
    ]
}