{
    "video_id": "KSiGMby_nLs",
    "title": "Living and working from an all-electric VW ID Buzz #shorts",
    "channel": "The Verge",
    "channel_id": "UCddiUEpeqJcYeBxX1IVBKvQ",
    "subscriber_count": 3390000,
    "upload_date": "2023-05-27T11:44:41Z",
    "video_url": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KSiGMby_nLs",
    "category": "Autos & Vehicles",
    "tags": [
        "vw",
        "ev",
        "vanlife",
        "cars",
        "tech",
        "volkswagen",
        "electric vehicle",
        "camping",
        "slice of life"
    ],
    "views": 76533,
    "likes": 1993,
    "comments_count": 44,
    "description": "Two humans and a beagle named Hank spent two weeks and 2,000 miles in Europe with an all-electric VW ID Buzz and Ququq camping box to preview the future of #vanlife.\n\nSubscribe: http://goo.gl/G5RXGs\nLike The Verge on Facebook: https://goo.gl/2P1aGc\nFollow on Twitter: https://goo.gl/XTWX61\nFollow on Instagram: https://goo.gl/7ZeLvX\nFollow on TikTok: http://bit.ly/42VeCVU\n\nThe Vergecast Podcast: https://pod.link/430333725\nDecoder with Nilay Patel: http://apple.co/3v29nDc \nMore about our podcasts: https://www.theverge.com/podcasts\n\nRead More: http://www.theverge.com\nCommunity guidelines: http://bit.ly/2D0hlAv\nWallpapers from The Verge: https://bit.ly/2xQXYJr\n\nSubscribe to The Vergecast on YouTube, new episodes on Wednesday and Friday: https://bit.ly/3I6nJtz",
    "description_links": [
        "http://goo.gl/G5RXGs",
        "https://goo.gl/2P1aGc",
        "https://goo.gl/XTWX61",
        "https://goo.gl/7ZeLvX",
        "http://bit.ly/42VeCVU",
        "https://pod.link/430333725",
        "http://apple.co/3v29nDc",
        "https://www.theverge.com/podcasts",
        "http://www.theverge.com",
        "http://bit.ly/2D0hlAv",
        "https://bit.ly/2xQXYJr",
        "https://bit.ly/3I6nJtz"
    ],
    "transcript": "I just spent two weeks and nearly 2,000 miles living and working from this all-electric Volkswagen ID Buzz to test the future of #vanlife. I used a BioLite BaseCharge 1500 with solar panel to provide continuous power to my StarLink space internet. That's because the ID Buzz can only power the van's AC outlet and USB ports, lighting and heater for up to 45 minutes at a time. To eat and sleep I installed this BusBox from QUQUQ. It's quick to set up, sleeps two adults and one dog named Hank comfortably, and the kitchen is a marvel of ingenuity. Even at $3,000 it's cheap compared to the premium VW will for the ID California camper that's still a few years away. The experience required fewer compromises than you might think, and without much range anxiety, thanks to Europe's mature network of ultra fast chargers. Like VW's charming electric van, we are still smiling. And that's before VW starts selling a bigger ID Buzz in the US next year. But there's no need to wait if you live in Europe, where #evanlife is now a reality.",
    "transcript_keywords": [
        "allelectric Volkswagen",
        "Volkswagen ID Buzz",
        "spent two weeks",
        "miles living",
        "living and working",
        "test the future",
        "Volkswagen",
        "Buzz",
        "StarLink space internet",
        "provide continuous power",
        "Buzz to test",
        "vanlife",
        "USB ports",
        "outlet and USB",
        "bigger ID Buzz",
        "space internet",
        "spent",
        "weeks",
        "miles",
        "living"
    ],
    "transcript_entities": [
        [
            "next year",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "up to 45 minutes",
            "TIME"
        ],
        [
            "#",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "two weeks",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "USB",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Volkswagen",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Hank",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "1500",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "California",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "AC",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Europe",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "US",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "a few years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "QUQUQ",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "3,000",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "VW",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "two",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Buzz",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "BioLite BaseCharge",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "nearly 2,000 miles",
            "QUANTITY"
        ]
    ]
}