{
    "video_id": "ZdxRJuvcQfM",
    "title": "Moto Z Droid Edition Hands-On",
    "channel": "MrMobile [Michael Fisher]",
    "channel_id": "UCSOpcUkE-is7u7c4AkLgqTw",
    "subscriber_count": 1250000,
    "upload_date": "2016-07-14T23:01:28Z",
    "video_url": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZdxRJuvcQfM",
    "category": "People & Blogs",
    "tags": [
        "moto z droid edition",
        "moto z hands on",
        "moto z force",
        "moto z force review",
        "moto z review",
        "moto z force hands on",
        "moto droid",
        "droid 2016",
        "verizon wireless",
        "mrmobile",
        "captain2phones",
        "michael fisher",
        "android central",
        "pocketnow",
        "mobile nations",
        "android authority",
        "moto z force droid edition"
    ],
    "views": 91483,
    "likes": 4323,
    "comments_count": 457,
    "description": "[UPDATE] Good news! The full MrMobile review of the Moto Z Droid Edition is now available, and it's a doozy! Check it out here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NmLU1aiqOL4\n\nI know, I know … you’ve seen this before. But when Lenovo rolled out the Moto Z in San Francisco last month, the only people who saw \"Moto Z Hands On\" from MrMobile were my Facebook friends. And while I *do* recommend you follow me on Facebook (ahem), this is one smartphone that deserves a proper video treatment for a first impression. I’m Michael Fisher and this is a quick Moto Z Droid Edition Hands On, featuring the Moto Z Droid Edition AND the Moto Z Force Droid Edition!\n\n\n[SUBSCRIBE]\n\nhttps://www.youtube.com/channel/UCSOpcUkE-is7u7c4AkLgqTw?sub_confirmation=1\n\n\n[ABOUT THIS HANDS-ON]\n\nThis video was produced after two hours of Moto Z hands-on time at a Verizon Wireless/Lenovo event in New York City, during which MrMobile received a Moto Z Droid Edition and Moto Z Force Droid Edition on loan for review. A full review is forthcoming. \n\n\n[SOCIALIZE]\n\nhttp://facebook.com/themrmobile\nhttp://instagram.com/themrmobile\nhttp://twitter.com/themrmobile\nhttps://www.snapchat.com/add/mrmobilesnaps\nhttp://mrmobile.tech\n\n\n[MUSIC]\n\n\"The Ballad of MrMobile\" (Mobile Nations, 2016)\n\n\"Overflowing\" by Score Squad, available at Premium Beat: http://www.premiumbeat.com/royalty_free_music/songs/overflowing\n\n\n[DISCLOSURE]\n\nThis post may contain affiliate links. See Mobile Nations' disclosure policy for more details: http://www.mobilenations.com/external-links/",
    "description_links": [
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NmLU1aiqOL4",
        "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCSOpcUkE-is7u7c4AkLgqTw?sub_confirmation=1",
        "http://facebook.com/themrmobile",
        "http://instagram.com/themrmobile",
        "http://twitter.com/themrmobile",
        "https://www.snapchat.com/add/mrmobilesnaps",
        "http://mrmobile.tech",
        "http://www.premiumbeat.com/royalty_free_music/songs/overflowing",
        "http://www.mobilenations.com/external-links/"
    ],
    "transcript": "- I know, I know. You've seen this before. But when Lenovo rolled out the Moto Z in San Francisco last month, the only people who saw the phone get the Mr. Mobile treatment were my Facebook friends. And while I do recommend you follow me on Facebook, this is one smartphone that deserves a second shot at a first impression. I'm Michael Fisher, and this is a quick look at the Moto Z Droid edition. Droid, of course, means Verizon Wireless, who hosted us at a New York launch event this morning to unveil the Moto Z Droid and Droid Force. They're calling the new Droid the world's thinnest premium smartphone at 5.2 millimeters. While the thicker Droid Force sacrifices that distinction for a larger battery, a higher res camera, and a second generation shatter shield display. Verizon also says the new Droid will revolutionize what you can do with a smartphone, and it's that claim that I'm most interested in testing. Because it's not just the phones I'm reviewing later this month. It's the mods. Both Droid Z and Droid Z Force allow you to customize them using one of four types of magnetic Moto mods. The simplest are the style shells. These are purely cosmetic. Think of them like a modern version of changeable battery doors. My review units came with wooden shells in the box. Yes, it is real wood. And you'll be able to choose from a range of colors and materials when the phones go on sale. You'll be able to choose which color chassis you want as well. The more advanced mods are the more exciting ones. They make use of the 16 pogo ports on the bottom of the Droid to expand its functionality. You've got a Tumi power pack, which adds another 2200 milliamp hours to the onboard battery. The JBL soundboost speaker with two three watt drivers. Its own 1000 milliamp hour battery and a kickstand, and the insta share projector, which turns your phone into, you guessed it, a projector. Lenovo was also showing off the Motomod developer kit coming this summer. Obviously the company hopes to entice Indie developers to build their own Moto Z add ons. In the hand, the Z is certainly a departure from the Motorolas of yesteryear. There's no curved back, no fingertip dimple, and its core is cold smooth aluminum. Also, I'd be remiss not to mention the elimination of the headphone jack. I've been using bluetooth headphones for years, so it's not that big a deal to me. If you feel differently though, Lenovo has smartly included a USB C adapter in the box. Also in there, a SIM tool, and a turbopower 15 or 30 charger for the Droid and Droid Force, respectively. And finally the software here is a close to stock Android Marshmallow with some Moto customizations which I like, and the usual Verizon bloatware, which I don't. I know you're all dying to know when these are launching and how much they'll cost, both with and without the Motomods, and I'm dying to tell you, just as soon as my full Moto Z review goes live. Until then, I'll be focused on answering these questions: how much functionality the Motomods bring. How much of Motorola's excellent software survived the transition to Lenovo. And whether I'll be buying one of these to serve as my personal daily driver, as I have done with almost every Moto Flagship since the first Moto X. It's gonna be a lot of fun. So make sure you're subscribed to Mr. Mobile on YouTube, so you don't miss out on my conclusions and hit me on the socials to tell me what else you want to know about the Moto Z, and thanks for watching. Until next week, stay mobile my friends.",
    "transcript_keywords": [
        "Droid",
        "Droid Force",
        "Moto",
        "thicker Droid Force",
        "Droid Force sacrifices",
        "Force",
        "Droid and Droid",
        "Moto Z Droid",
        "San Francisco",
        "Lenovo",
        "Droid edition",
        "thicker Droid",
        "Verizon",
        "Facebook",
        "Moto Flagship",
        "Moto mods",
        "battery",
        "Michael Fisher",
        "Verizon Wireless",
        "Mobile"
    ],
    "transcript_entities": [
        [
            "Lenovo",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Motorolas",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "this summer",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Verizon",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "1000 milliamp hour",
            "QUANTITY"
        ],
        [
            "5.2 millimeters",
            "QUANTITY"
        ],
        [
            "Verizon",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "15 or 30",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "San Francisco",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Motomods",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "YouTube",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "four",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Facebook",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "JBL",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Verizon Wireless",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Moto",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Mobile",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "last month",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Moto Z Droid",
            "PRODUCT"
        ],
        [
            "Motorola",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Android Marshmallow",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "this morning",
            "TIME"
        ],
        [
            "16",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Moto Z",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "USB C",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Motomods",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "three watt",
            "QUANTITY"
        ],
        [
            "Tumi",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "jack",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Motomod",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "two",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Droid",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Moto Flagship",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "second",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Moto Z Droid and Droid Force",
            "PRODUCT"
        ],
        [
            "New York",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "next week",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Michael Fisher",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "later this month",
            "DATE"
        ]
    ]
}