{
    "video_id": "uq7lwIAyzb0",
    "title": "Headphones That Boom?",
    "channel": "Unbox Therapy",
    "channel_id": "UCsTcErHg8oDvUnTzoqsYeNw",
    "subscriber_count": 24800000,
    "upload_date": "2016-04-12T17:10:38Z",
    "video_url": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uq7lwIAyzb0",
    "category": "Science & Technology",
    "tags": [
        "boomstick",
        "boomcloud",
        "headphones",
        "boomcloud 360",
        "best headphones",
        "best",
        "unboxtherapy",
        "unbox therapy",
        "audio",
        "tech",
        "technology",
        "beats",
        "iphone",
        "earbuds",
        "earpods",
        "apple",
        "review",
        "unboxing",
        "iphone 6s",
        "android",
        "samsung",
        "6s",
        "smartphone",
        "galaxy",
        "iphone 6",
        "phone",
        "test",
        "new",
        "s7",
        "iphone 6s plus",
        "android (operating system)",
        "comparison",
        "vs",
        "iphone 7",
        "apple iphone",
        "apple iphone 6s",
        "apple inc. (publisher)",
        "galaxy s7",
        "galaxy s7 edge",
        "s7 edge",
        "smartphone (video game platform)",
        "s6",
        "edge",
        "case",
        "gadgets",
        "crazy",
        "fire",
        "top"
    ],
    "views": 1652383,
    "likes": 37769,
    "comments_count": 2889,
    "description": "BoomStick - http://amzn.to/1qYlVJd\n\nFOLLOW ME IN THESE PLACES FOR UPDATES\nTwitter - http://twitter.com/unboxtherapy\nFacebook - http://facebook.com/lewis.hilsenteger\nInstagram - http://instagram.com/unboxtherapy\nGoogle Plus - http://bit.ly/1auEeak",
    "description_links": [
        "http://amzn.to/1qYlVJd",
        "http://twitter.com/unboxtherapy",
        "http://facebook.com/lewis.hilsenteger",
        "http://instagram.com/unboxtherapy",
        "http://bit.ly/1auEeak"
    ],
    "transcript": "Hey como estn? Lew aqu, de vuelta con otro video, Y hoy tengo algo que me emociona. Esto se llama BOOMSTICK, Y lo que hace es tomar tus viejos audfonos. y al parecer mejora el rendimiento de audio En algunas diferentes maneras Es como un amplificador de audio externo Pero tambin hace ciertas cosas inteligentes Tiene algunos algoritmos instalados para buscar a travez de una cancin en tiempo real cuando la ests escuchando Y hace algunos ajustes con el fin de supuestamente mejorar tu experiencia Claro que yo voy a probar esa teora conectar este aparato a un par de audfonos y tambin a unos audfonos mas elaborados y ver si peso escuchar la diferencia, hagmoslo batera recargable, porttil, ligero, 12 horas de uso por carga esta bien siento que agarro el concepto la gente est considerando la calidad del audio y mucho de eso tiene que ver con el volumen y en muchos casos en tus audfonos solamente no estas recibiendo mucho volumen cuando estoy en un avian y tienes eel sonido de este el chatter, el bebe llorando por ahi y muchos problemas cuando tu estas considering whether or not you're getting a quality listening experience has to do with volume so amplification plays a big role in fact if you show most people to audio sources one is louder than the other it tends to color their perspective many times people will just pick the latter source because they think louder is better so there's the device itself micro USB on one side little power switch on the other headphone jack up here on the top a touch button your mini jack connector on the other side cool a little carrying case this is one that I'm pretty confident I have figured out here I got it first thing I want to do here I want to use some standard earpods everybody has them, you're in high school, in the cafeteria you can't get away from these things first step is to listen without the boomstick Well let's do the BOOMSTICK WOW Way more volume Like substantially maybe twice as much volume I listen to a lot of podcasts, maybe i should take these out im yelling And many times for better for worse a lot of podcasting come out quiet this just solved that problem for me right I wanna take a bigger set of headphones here do a quick test without the BOOMSTiCK taken in with way more low end, just by default way bigger driver look at guy what about when we BOOMSTICK it ok thats blasting that's more volume than I would ever normally use right there i tested music, but what about the dialogue let's check it woah that sounded incredible let me just oh my goodness ok this might even be more substantial of an improvement compared to the music yeah so I think this device pays even more dividends for dialogue the boomstick enhance your headphones with the tiny little device like this any opportunity to offer below the amplification from your mobile device to something more substantial is going to have an impact whether it's for music or for dialogue, movies or podcasting I can confidently say that this guy right here will help you with that so check them out boomstick Jack look at that how cute is that I don't use that word cute often but when I do it's very important that cute.",
    "transcript_keywords": [
        "Hey como estn",
        "BOOMSTICK",
        "Hey como",
        "como estn",
        "con otro video",
        "vuelta con otro",
        "Pero tambin hace",
        "hoy tengo algo",
        "BOOMSTICK WOW",
        "tus viejos audfonos",
        "audfonos",
        "boomstick Jack",
        "audio externo Pero",
        "volume",
        "audio",
        "tus audfonos solamente",
        "mucho volumen cuando",
        "device",
        "externo Pero tambin",
        "con"
    ],
    "transcript_entities": [
        [
            "al",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "hagmoslo batera",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Y lo que hace es tomar tus",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "12",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "mejora el rendimiento de audio",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "de vuelta con otro video",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "USB",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "por ahi",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "ligero",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "y mucho de eso tiene que ver",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Y hoy tengo algo que",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "maneras Es como un",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Jack",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "horas de uso por carga",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Claro que yo voy",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "unos",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "para buscar",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "BOOMSTiCK",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "cuando estoy en un",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "cuando la ests",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Lew aqu",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "probar esa teora conectar este aparato a",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "de una cancin en tiempo",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "mas elaborados",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Pero",
            "PRODUCT"
        ],
        [
            "un",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "viejos audfonos",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "el bebe llorando",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Y hace algunos ajustes",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ]
    ]
}