{
    "video_id": "pNd5_kxpPc4",
    "title": "The Best Mac... Apple Doesn't Make!",
    "channel": "Snazzy Labs",
    "channel_id": "UCO2x-p9gg9TLKneXlibGR7w",
    "subscriber_count": 1170000,
    "upload_date": "2017-01-27T03:00:37Z",
    "video_url": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pNd5_kxpPc4",
    "category": "Science & Technology",
    "tags": [
        "best mac",
        "snazzy labs",
        "mac pro amd",
        "2017 mac pro",
        "snazzyq",
        "mac",
        "mac pro upgrade",
        "hackintosh pro",
        "mac pro 2013 upgrade",
        "mac pro nvidia",
        "macbook pro vs mac pro",
        "fastest mac",
        "macbook egpu",
        "mac egpu",
        "mac pro egpu",
        "final cut pro egpu",
        "amd rx480",
        "amd macbook pro",
        "supercharge macbook",
        "external gpu",
        "egpu",
        "overview",
        "snazzy",
        "make mac pro great again",
        "frankenmac",
        "the best mac apple doesn't make",
        "akitio node",
        "the best mac apple doesnt make",
        "apple",
        "best mac apple doesn't make"
    ],
    "views": 749567,
    "likes": 29227,
    "comments_count": 2393,
    "description": "40% off Slickwraps through the end of January! - http://snazzy.fm/slick\n\nParts used for GPU enclosure:\nAMD RX480 - http://amzn.to/2kkriV1\nAkitio Thunder2 (will require modification) - http://amzn.to/2l1bL9H\nFractal Node 304 case - http://amzn.to/2lcTpV5\n\nApple hasn't updated Mac Pro since 2013. They might not care, but WE do! Let's update and benchmark the Mac Pro CPU and the Mac Pro GPU to an eGPU AMD RX480 so we can make Apple's oldest Mac their fastest Mac with this tech overview!",
    "description_links": [
        "http://snazzy.fm/slick",
        "http://amzn.to/2kkriV1",
        "http://amzn.to/2l1bL9H",
        "http://amzn.to/2lcTpV5"
    ],
    "transcript": "Nearly a year ago, I published a video about how the $4,000 Mac Pro was incredibly antiquated and couldnt edit 4K video to the caliber that I required, so I moved to Windows. Its now 2017 and Apple STILL hasnt updated the Mac Prosince 2013despite the fact its still sold in Apple Stores at full price. Ive recently moved from Adobe Premiere to Final Cut Pro; which means I need a Mac again. I bought the fully-loaded $4,000 2016 MacBook Pro, but its price tag couldnt justify the bugs, under clocked CPU, and dismal GPU performance; so I returned it, and decided to do something crazytear apart my old Mac Pro, upgrade the CPU, RAM, and add an external GPU so that I could outperform the best iMac, MacBook Pro, and even the $8,000 Mac Pro. It workedand it only cost 1,000 bucks. The first task was finding a compatible CPUand it turns out, there arent many. The highest-end compatible CPU is the Intel Xeon E5-2697v2 which is an Ivy Bridge 12-core 2.7GHz processor with 3.5GHz Turbo Boost. Apple charges a whopping $3,000 upgrade, but there are a ton of retired server CPUs on eBay for around $600. I bought one, disassembled the Mac Prowhich, by the way, was surprisingly user-serviceable for an Apple productand popped the new one in. I also decided to upgrade the DDR3 ECC memory which has come down in price significantly. I bought 32GB of compatible RAM on Amazon for $160. Apple charges $400 for this upgrade. My last upgrade was ditching my dependence on the crappy, outdated dual AMD FirePro D300 graphics cards in the machine. The new MacBook Pro uses an AMD Radeon 460 which is built on the new Polaris architecture which means macOS now natively supports the latest-gen AMD graphics cardslike the $250 RX 480 I chose to use. No weird drivers. No heavy modification of system files, it just works. And thats spectacular. I jammed the GPU, modified Akitio PCI-e to Thunderbolt 2 dock, and an overkill 350W power supply into a makeshift Fractal Design Node 202 PC case. I used nice Fractal fans which makes for a dead-silent operation. Keep in mind, the Mac Pro uses the old Thunderbolt 2 which means were not getting the full performance of the graphics card; however, the 60% bandwidth that I was able to achieve using the RX 480 FAR supersedes any other Mac that Apple sells. Dont believe me? Lets look at the benchmarks of my new FrankenMac! Since the CPU in FrankenMac is the same as the loaded Mac Pro, the benchmark results are the same. In Geekbench, the new MacBook Pro has a faster single-core score due to the low clock-speed on the 12-core CPU in FrankenMac, but multi-core performance crushes both the stock Mac Pro and the loaded MacBook Pro. In Cinebench, the CPU pulls ahead yet again clocking in at nearly 3 times faster than the 2016 MacBook Pro. Now, we get to the graphics card benchmarks. FrankenMacs AMD RX480 is 40% than the stock Mac Pro and 35% faster than the $8,000 Mac Pro. In Unigine Heaven, the RX480 did much poorer than the NVIDIA GTX980 Ti I tested on the Mac Pro last year which clocked in at 51 FPS, but the RX480 still outperforms the other cards in Apple machines. Thats all well and good, but what about real-world performance? In Final Cut Pro, a demo project I exported compressing 4K ProRes footage to H.264 with FrankenMac was 275% faster than the base Mac Pro and 2016 MacBook Pro. A base Mac Pro can be found used on eBay for about $1,500. So, for $2,500, you can build your own FrankenMac. Is it faster than comparable $2,500 PC hardware? No. But its a heck of a lot faster than anything else Apple makes.",
    "transcript_keywords": [
        "Mac Pro",
        "Pro",
        "MacBook Pro",
        "stock Mac Pro",
        "Mac",
        "base Mac Pro",
        "Final Cut Pro",
        "loaded Mac Pro",
        "Apple",
        "Cut Pro",
        "Mac Prosince",
        "CPU",
        "Apple Stores",
        "moved to Windows",
        "MacBook",
        "stock Mac",
        "incredibly antiquated",
        "base Mac",
        "loaded MacBook Pro",
        "Windows"
    ],
    "transcript_entities": [
        [
            "32GB",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "275%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "2017",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "8,000",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "K ProRes",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "about $1,500",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "250",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "Cinebench",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Adobe Premiere to Final Cut Pro",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "AMD FirePro D300",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Thunderbolt 2",
            "PRODUCT"
        ],
        [
            "2,500",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "MacBook Pro",
            "EVENT"
        ],
        [
            "FPS",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the Mac Prosince",
            "WORK_OF_ART"
        ],
        [
            "4,000",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "3,000",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "Apple",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "eBay",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "last year",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Turbo Boost",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "35%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "FrankenMac",
            "EVENT"
        ],
        [
            "350W",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "RX480",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Intel Xeon E5-2697v2",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "1,000 bucks",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "51",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "RX480",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "GPU",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "FrankenMac",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Mac",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "around $600",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "40%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "Mac Pro",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Final Cut Pro",
            "WORK_OF_ART"
        ],
        [
            "2.7GHz",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Fractal Design Node",
            "PRODUCT"
        ],
        [
            "NVIDIA",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "12",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the Mac Pro",
            "PRODUCT"
        ],
        [
            "CPU",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Fractal",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "RAM",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "4",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the Mac Prowhich",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Windows",
            "PRODUCT"
        ],
        [
            "AMD Radeon 460",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "MacBook Pro",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "AMD",
            "PRODUCT"
        ],
        [
            "Amazon",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "202",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "iMac",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "60%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "Polaris",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "2016",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "3.5GHz",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Apple Stores",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Akitio PCI-e",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "DDR3 ECC",
            "PRODUCT"
        ],
        [
            "nearly 3",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "CPUand",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "a ton",
            "QUANTITY"
        ],
        [
            "400",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "macOS",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Geekbench",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Nearly a year ago",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "160",
            "MONEY"
        ]
    ]
}